# HEATHER **HAYES**

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 

# **ABOUT ME**

Dedicated and adaptable professional with over a decade of customer service experience, now transitioning to a career in technology through comprehensive learning at Holberton Tulsa. Passionate about continuous growth, effective communication, and contributing to a diverse and vibrant tech community.

# CONTACT



918-237-6074



Downtown Tulsa



github.com/hayes28



heather.hayes918@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/heatherhayes



hireheather918.com

# SOFT SKILLS

**Effective Communication** 

**Problem Solving** 

Leadership & Teamwork

Attention to Detail

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML	CSS
Git	SASS
React	Flask
Notion	Figma
Slack	Docker
GitHub	Python
MySQL	jQuery
node.js	Firebase
Bootstrap	REST API
ccessibility	JavaScrip
JI/UX design	Bash Scripti

# **PROJECTS**

# THE VELVET WILLOW - GROUP PROJECT

Revamped a vintage furniture rental site of local business

- Used Firebase for data management
- Structured a reviews.json for customer feedback
- Collaborated with the client to craft an inviting UI/UX design

July 2023

# **GLOBAL SKY MOSAIC - GROUP PROJECT**

- Developed a Weather Application in a 4-day Hack Sprint
- Integrated WeatherAPI for real-time updates
- Provides campus-specific weather information and photos
- Delegated tasks to complete project in timely manner
- Contributed to UI/UX and project design

May 2023

#### **DESIGNER LANGUAGE - GROUP PROJECT**

- 3-part UX project for Spotify desktop application
- Conducted research, prototyping, and validation
- Blog post available on LinkedIn

## **EDUCATION**

#### **HOLBERTON TULSA**

Full Stack certificate & Diploma in Computer Science

- Equips students with comprehensive full-stack web development
- Emphasizes project-based learning and problem-solving
- Fosters diverse networks and successful tech careers

#### TULSA COMMUNITY COLLEGE

2011-2015 Tulsa, OK

### Associates of Liberal Arts/ Psychology

- Provides diverse academic programs, including associate degrees, certificates, and workforce training
- Prioritizes accessibility, affordability, and inclusivity for all students
- Fosters success through quality teaching and support services

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **GOLDIES PATIO GRILL, TULSA**

2010-2020

Tulsa, OK

#### **Shift Leader**

Encouraged feedback to boosted team efficiency and morale

- Reduced to-go order errors with a double-check system
- Streamlined peak-hour operations with role coordination
- Managed daily financials and banking tasks

#### Server

ng

- Efficiently handled orders, payments, and drink preparation
- Supported kitchen prep tasks for efficiency
- Provided exceptional customer service
- Maintained cleanliness standards

June 2023



2022-2024

Tulsa, OK